[{
        "question": "On my honor I will do my ...",
        "choices": ["duty", "best", "job"],
        "correctAns": 1
    }, {
        "question": "To do my duty to _ and my country ",
        "choices": ["God", "the den", "the pack"],
        "correctAns": 0
    }, {
        "question": "and to _ the Scout Law",
        "choices": ["uphold", "follow", "obey"],
        "correctAns": 2
    }, {
        "question": "To help other people at ...",
        "choices": ["all times", "in all ways", "in all places"],
        "correctAns": 0
    }, {
        "question": "To keep myself _ strong,",
        "choices": ["emotionally", "mentally", "physically"],
        "correctAns": 2
    }, {
        "question": "mentally awake, and morally _ .",
        "choices": ["straight", "upright", "honest"],
        "correctAns": 0
    }, {
        "question": "A Scout is _",
        "choices": ["trustworthy", "honest", "hardworking"],
        "correctAns": 0
    }, {
        "question": "A Scout is trustworthy, loyal, helpful, friendly, _",
        "choices": ["clean", "courteous", "thrifty"],
        "correctAns": 1
    }, {
        "question": "A Scout is trustworthy, loyal, helpful, friendly, courteous, kind, obedient, _",
        "choices": ["happy", "joyful", "cheerful"],
        "correctAns": 2
    }, {
        "question": "A Scout is hungry!",
        "choices": ["True"],
        "correctAns": 0
    }

]